{
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "What percentage of greenhouse gas emissions in New Zealand are produced by agriculture?",
            "answer": 48.1
        },
        {
            "question": "Per capita, how much carbon dioxide and other greenhouse gas is emitted when flying Auckland to Heathrow, London return? (kg)",
            "answer": 7796
        },
        {
            "question": "How much of New Zealand’s electricity is generated from renewable resources? %",
            "answer": 82
        },
        {
            "question": "How much of New Zealand’s greeen house gas emissions are from generating electricity? %",
            "answer": 5
        },
        {
            "question": "How many single-use plastic bags were distributed in New Zealand in 2018?",
            "answer": 750000000
        },
        {
            "question": "On average, each New Zealand household wastes how many dollars every year from throwing out food?",
            "answer": 563
        },
        {
            "question": "How much e-waste is produced in New Zealand each year? (tonnes)",
            "answer": 95000
        },
        {
            "question": "How fast is a peregrine falcon? km/h",
            "answer": 360
        },
        {
            "question": "How fast is a cheetah? km/h",
            "answer": 105
        },
        {
            "question": "How fast is a peregrine lion? km/h",
            "answer": 80
        },
        {
            "question": "What percentage of greenhouse gas emissions in New Zealand are produced by energy and road transport?",
            "answer": 40.7
        }

    ],
    "attacks": [
        {
            "name": "Swipe",
            "selfDefense": 0,
            "selfAttack": 0,
            "enemyDefense": 0,
            "enemyAttack": 5,
            "maxUses": 50
        },
        {
            "name": "Scare",
            "selfDefense": -1,
            "selfAttack": 2,
            "enemyDefense": 7,
            "enemyAttack": 0,
            "maxUses": 25
        },
        {
            "name": "Bite",
            "selfDefense": 1,
            "selfAttack": 1,
            "enemyDefense": 2,
            "enemyAttack": 5,
            "maxUses": 25
        },
        {
            "name": "Grab",
            "selfDefense": 1,
            "selfAttack": 1,
            "enemyDefense": 8,
            "enemyAttack": 0,
            "maxUses": 15
        },
        {
            "name": "Claw",
            "selfDefense": 0,
            "selfAttack": 0,
            "enemyDefense": -2,
            "enemyAttack": 8,
            "maxUses": 15
        },
        {
            "name": "Jump",
            "selfDefense": 7,
            "selfAttack": 0,
            "enemyDefense": 0,
            "enemyAttack": 0,
            "maxUses": 50
        },
        {
            "name": "Takedown",
            "selfDefense": 0,
            "selfAttack": 0,
            "enemyDefense": -2,
            "enemyAttack": 11,
            "maxUses": 15
        },
        {
            "name": "Empty",
            "selfDefense": 0,
            "selfAttack": 0,
            "enemyDefense": 0,
            "enemyAttack": 0,
            "maxUses": 0
        }
    ],
    "dinos": [
        {
            "name": "Basic",
            "hp": 10,
            "attack": 1,
            "defense": 0,
            "attacks": [
                "Swipe",
                "Swipe",
                "Swipe"
            ]
        },
        {
            "name": "Springy",
            "hp": 10,
            "attack": 1,
            "defense": 0,
            "attacks": [
                "Jump",
                "Jump",
                "Claw"
            ]
        },
        {
            "name": "Spiney",
            "hp": 10,
            "attack": 1,
            "defense": 0,
            "attacks": [
                "Takedown",
                "Bite",
                "Scare"
            ]
        },
        {
            "name": "Strengthy",
            "hp": 10,
            "attack": 1,
            "defense": 0,
            "attacks": [
                "Grab",
                "Grab",
                "Claw"
            ]
        },
        {
            "name": "Ghosty",
            "hp": 10,
            "attack": 1,
            "defense": 0,
            "attacks": [
                "Scare",
                "Scare",
                "Jump"
            ]
        },
        {
            "name": "Nasty",
            "hp": 10,
            "attack": 1,
            "defense": 0,
            "attacks": [
                "Empty",
                "Empty",
                "Scare"
            ]
        },
        {
            "name": "Empty",
            "hp": 0,
            "attack": 0,
            "defense": 0,
            "attacks": [
                "Empty",
                "Empty",
                "Empty"
            ]
        }
    ]
}